<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comment on </title>
    <link>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comment on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GetComment</title>
      <link>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_get_comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_get_comment/</guid>
      <description>jiraGetComment This step queries a particular comment on an issue.
Input  idOrKey - Issue id or key. commentId - commentId. site - Optional, default: JIRA_SITE environment variable. failOnError - Optional. default: true.  Output  Each step generates generic output, please refer to this link for more information. The api response of this jira_get_comment step can be reused later in your script by doing response.data.required_field_name. You can see some example scenarios here All the available fields for a JIRA response can be found in JIRA API documentation depending on your JIRA version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GetComments</title>
      <link>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_get_comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_get_comments/</guid>
      <description>jiraGetComments This step queries all comments on a particular issue.
Input  idOrKey - Issue id or key. site - Optional, default: JIRA_SITE environment variable. failOnError - Optional. default: true.  Output  Each step generates generic output, please refer to this link for more information. The api response of this jira_get_comments step can be reused later in your script by doing response.data.required_field_name. You can see some example scenarios here All the available fields for a jira response can be found in JIRA API documentation depending on your JIRA version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AddComment</title>
      <link>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_add_comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_add_comment/</guid>
      <description>jiraAddComment This step adds a comment on a particular issue.
Input  idOrKey - Issue id or key. input - comment, supports jira wiki formatting. site - Optional, default: JIRA_SITE environment variable. failOnError - Optional. default: true. auditLog - Optional. default: true. Append a panel to the comment with the build url and build user name. Deprecated: comment - comment, supports jira wiki formatting.  Output  Each step generates generic output, please refer to this link for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EditComment</title>
      <link>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_edit_comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jenkinsci.github.io/jira-steps-plugin/steps/comment/jira_edit_comment/</guid>
      <description>jiraEditComment This step updates a particular comment on particular issue.
Input  idOrKey - Issue id or key. commentId - comment id. input - comment, supports jira wiki formatting. site - Optional, default: JIRA_SITE environment variable. failOnError - Optional. default: true. Deprecated: comment - comment, supports jira wiki formatting.  Output  Each step generates generic output, please refer to this link for more information. The api response of this jira_edit_comment step can be reused later in your script by doing response.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>